what's up barbin family as you all know
we spend a ton of time here covering all
things Fitness from our strength weekly
podcast to covering events like the
CrossFit Games as well as reviewing the
best fitness equipment and supplements
in the game now I'm really excited
because we've got a brand new channel
that's going to be dedicated
specifically to reviews content titled
barbend reviews while this channel will
still serve as your One-Stop shop for
all other Fitness related content so if
you're looking to fill out your home gym
with new gear or you're like me and
you're just obsessed with fitness
equipment then head over and click that
shiny subscribe button cuz we've got a
lot of exciting things in store you
definitely don't want to miss
out